<resources>
    <string name="long_slogan_1">Love is not about finding the perfect person, but about learning to see perfection in someone\'s imperfections. When we truly love someone, we accept their flaws, their mistakes, and even the scars on their soul. Because love isn\'t about changing each other — it\'s about growing together to become better versions of ourselves. To love is to mature together, to smile together, no matter how much the world changes.</string>
    <string name="long_slogan_2">Love is like a flame — if it burns only with emotion, it will fade quickly; but if it\'s fueled by trust and understanding, it will never go out. Every gentle word, every held hand, every act of forgiveness becomes the spark that keeps it alive. And when two people choose to cherish each other every single day, love becomes the calmest warmth in a stormy world.</string>
    <string name="long_slogan_3">Love doesn\'t need to be loud or showy — just a look that understands, an embrace that feels safe, and two hearts always reaching for each other. Sometimes silence between two people speaks louder than a thousand promises. When you find someone whose presence alone makes you feel at peace, that\'s real love — simple yet enduring, quiet yet profoundly deep.</string>
    <string name="long_slogan_4">In love, it doesn\'t matter who comes first or who loves more — what truly matters is who stays until the end. Because love isn\'t possession; it\'s companionship. It\'s seeing that person happy, even if their joy doesn\'t always include you. It\'s choosing to stay, not because you need someone, but because you can\'t imagine life without them.</string>
    <string name="long_slogan_5">Love is the journey of two imperfect people creating something perfect together. There will be moments of anger, misunderstanding, and pain — but those are what make love real and strong. When two hearts learn to listen, to forgive, and still choose to hold hands, their love has already withstood the test of time.</string>
    <string name="long_slogan_6">Love is not just a fleeting emotion — it\'s a choice. A choice to trust, to be patient, to stay. Today might be hard, but if we keep choosing each other despite everything, that\'s true love. Because real love doesn\'t say, “I need you,” but softly whispers, “I choose you, every day.”</string>
    <string name="long_slogan_7">Some loves don\'t need forever promises — just waking up and seeing that person beside you is enough. Happiness isn\'t found in grand gestures, but in the small moments shared: a meal together, a shared laugh, a quiet glance. Love isn\'t measured by years, but by the peaceful moments two hearts create together.</string>
    <string name="long_slogan_8">Love teaches us patience, compassion, and how to place “us” above “me.” Things won\'t always be easy, but in difficult times we realize how precious it is to have someone who stays. A beautiful love isn\'t one without tears — it\'s one where, even through tears, you can still smile because you know you\'re not alone.</string>
    <string name="long_slogan_9">Love doesn\'t make life easier, but it gives us a reason to smile through the struggles. When you love the right person, even the simplest things become meaningful — the morning sunlight, the afternoon rain, or just the sound of their voice. Because love isn\'t found in grand moments, but in how two people make each other feel “at home,” no matter where they are.</string>
    <string name="long_slogan_10">Love is not just about sweet words or romantic moments, but about understanding, forgiveness, and standing together through life\'s storms. When two hearts beat as one, every hardship feels lighter and every joy becomes fuller. True love doesn\'t need to be perfect — it only needs to be sincere and steadfast. Because in a world that changes every single day, holding someone\'s hand and walking through the years together is the simplest yet most precious miracle of all.</string>
</resources>
